Remember this, as you gained fame, as you gained fortune, as you gained position and
seniority, people will treat you better.
They will hold doors open for you.
They will get you a cup of tea and coffee without you even asking.
They will call you Sir and Ma'am, and they will give you stuff.
None of that stuff is meant for you.
That stuff is meant for the position you hold.
It is meant for the level that you have achieved of leader, or success, or whatever you want
to call it, but you will always deserve a styrofoam cup.
Remember that.
Remember that lesson of humility and gratitude.
You can accept all the free stuff.
You can accept all the perks.
Absolutely you can enjoy them but just be grateful for them and know that they are not
for you.